<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apt on </title>
    <link>/tags/apt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apt on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/apt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Boss Linux</title>
      <link>/bosslinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bosslinux/</guid>
      <description>BOSS LINUX The BOSS GNU/Linux Version 6 is coupled with GNOME Desktop Environment 3.14 with wide Indian language support &amp;amp; packages, relevant for use in the Government domain. This aims more at enhancing the user interface with more glossy themes and Tab like look and feel on the desktop by coupling latest applications.
BOSS (Bharat Operating System Solutions) is a GNU/Linux distribution developed by C-DAC, Chennai in order to benefit the usage of Free/Open Source Software in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepin OS</title>
      <link>/deepinos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/deepinos/</guid>
      <description>DEEPIN OS Deepin, stylized as deepin was formerly known as Linux Deepin and Hiweed Linux. What sets Deepin apart from other Linux Distributions is the is the strategic partner of CodeWeavers who packaged a TidBit into Deepin named &amp;ldquo;CrossOver&amp;rdquo;.
CrossOver is a Microsoft Windows compatibility layer for Linux. This layer enables Windows-based applications to run on Linux OSs.
Deepin features its own desktop environment called Deepin Desktop Environment (DDE), which is written in Qt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDE Neon</title>
      <link>/kdeneon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kdeneon/</guid>
      <description>KDE Neon KDE neon is a set of software repositories for Ubuntu long-term support (LTS) releases with latest 64-bit version of KDE desktop and applications.It is also the name given to a Ubuntu LTS-based Linux distribution that utilizes said repositories.It aims to provide the users with rapidly updated Qt and KDE software, while updating the rest of the OS components from the Ubuntu repositories at the normal pace. It comes in user and developer editions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu</title>
      <link>/kubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Kubuntu Kubuntu is an official flavour of the Ubuntu operating system which uses the KDE Plasma Desktop instead of the GNOME desktop environment. As part of the Ubuntu project, Kubuntu uses the same underlying systems. Every package in Kubuntu shares the same repositories as Ubuntu, and it is released regularly on the same schedule as Ubuntu.
&amp;ldquo;Kubuntu&amp;rdquo; is derived from the name Ubuntu, prefixing a K to represent the KDE platform Kubuntu is built upon (following a widespread naming convention of prefixing K to the name of any software released for use on KDE platforms), as well as the KDE community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Mint</title>
      <link>/linuxmint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linuxmint/</guid>
      <description>Linux Mint Linux Mint is a community-driven Linux distribution based on Debian and Ubuntu that strives to be a &amp;ldquo;modern, elegant and comfortable operating system which is both powerful and easy to use.&amp;rdquo;
Linux Mint provides full out-of-the-box multimedia support by including some proprietary software and comes bundled with a variety of free and open-source applications.
Linux Mint is a stable, robust, and elegant Ubuntu-based distribution.
Linux Mint is a great ‘default’ distro for new Linux users, as it comes with a lot of the software you’ll need when switching from Mac or Windows, such as LibreOffice, the favoured productivity suite of Linux users.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>